Guide to the Washington State University Audio/Video Materials 1930-2005
Washington State University Libraries Manuscripts, Archives, and Special Collections
- SERIES 2: RECRUITMENT AND PROMOTIONAL MEDIA.
  - WSU 1890-1990 retrospective. Tape is labeled "WSU Centennial 1890-1990" 14:56 3-11-89. Video: VHS. 15 min (Box 9, Item 13)
  - WSU: Making a Difference for Washington State. RXL Pulitzer Spokane produced. Video: VHS. 14:30, 1994-10 (Box 9, Item 14)
  - WSU: Making a Difference for Washington State. RXL Pulitzer (Spokane). Video: VHS. 14:30, 1994-10 (Box 9, Item 15)
  - WSU: Making a Difference for Washington State. Loop tape. Video: VHS. 14:30, 1994-10 (Box 9, Item 16)
- SERIES 3: CAMPUS STOCK FOOTAGE / B-ROLL.
    - WSU Stock Footage: Pullman Campus. Video: Betacam SP, undated (Box 10, Item 1)
    - 1940s WSU scenes: masters. Video: 3/4" U-matic (Box 10, Item 2)
    - WSU Aerials. Nose 3 Side 3. Video: 3/4" U-matic, 1991-06 (Box 10, Item 3)
    - "Isn't It Amazing"/National Girls and Women in Sports Day. 34 sec PSA followed by ~10 min. WSU campus footage. Video: 3/4" U-matic. ~11 min., 1995 February 04 (Box 10, Item 4)
    - Fall shots of WSU. Video only Dub from MII. Video: 3/4" U-matic. ~20 min., 1996 October 16 (Box 10, Item 5)
    - Pullman campus scenes. Video: 3/4" U-matic. 7:30, undated (Box 10, Item 6)
    - Campus Scenes - Fall 1986. Video: 3/4" U-matic (small). 20 min. (Box 10, Item 7)
    - Campus Scenes - Fall 1987. Video: 3/4" U-matic (small). 20 min. (Box 10, Item 8)
    - B roll - WSU Tri-Cities. Video: 3/4" U-matic (small). 20' tape, 1992 September 28 (Box 10, Item 9)
    - WSU-Spokane. Downtown from Cliff Drive, Entrance 1st Ave, Various students. Video: 3/4" U-matic (small). 20 min., 1992 October 01 (Box 10, Item 10)
    - "Admissions #12" on tape. Note in sleeve on front of tape case crosses out "Admissions" and labels "Minority Affairs" Index then lists shots from Stimson and Stevens dorms. Video: 3/4" U-matic (small). 20 min., undated (Box 10, Item 11)
    - KWSU-TV VC 20455 Slide Show. Video: 3/4" U-matic (small), undated (Box 10, Item 12)
    - "Material for use in WSU birthday promotional spot. List enclosed." Case and tape similar label except tape notes color and original. List foldered indicates shots of campus buildings. VC 32051 on case spine VC 230 on tape. Video: 3/4" U-matic (small). 20, undated (Box 10, Item 13)
    - Handwritten notes describing video components of tape 13. Paper., undated (Box 10, Item 0)
    - "Campus activities for use in football half-time promotions" on case. Tape has adhesive label "material for spots - B-day spot" Tape #228. VC 32047 on case spine VC 228 on tape. Video: 3/4" U-matic (small). 20 min.", 19uu-03-24 (Box 10, Item 14)
    - Handwritten notes describing video components of tape 14. Paper., undated (Box 10, Item 0)
    - "Material shot for promotional spots. List enclosed. (includes campus in winter!). Video: 3/4" U-matic (small). 20 min., undated (Box 10, Item 15)
    - Handwritten notes describing video components of tape 15. Paper., undated (Box 10, Item 0)
    - "Material of campus activities shot to promotional spots (first videotape of a laser: would it show up???)" also "Cover shots girl in lab Cow in hospital lasers" all on case cover. Tape is labeled "material for spots" with color and original noted. VC 320, undated (Box 10, Item 16)
    - WSU Tri-Cities B-Roll. Video: VHS. 120' tape, 1992 September 28 (Box 11, Item 1)
    - WSU Student Reel Fall 93-Spring 95. Video: VHS. 17:45, 1993-1995 (Box 11, Item 2)
    - WSU b-roll. Video: VHS, undated (Box 11, Item 3)
    - Campus Scenes. Video: Betacam SP, 2002 September 04 (Box 11, Item 4)
    - Campus scenes. Video: Betacam, 2002 September 04 (Box 11, Item 5)
    - Various B-roll footage from WSU. Video: Betacam SP. 30' tape, undated (Box 11, Item 6)
    - Shots about campus (WSC) about 1930. Label is taped on side. Label on top is Pathe Laboratory sticker with "Meet Dr. Chris?" and "Reel 4". Film: 16mm - silent, b/w. 300' of film (Box 11, Item 7)
    - WSU Coliseum Construction. From June Bierbower of the News Bureau. "Place in Historical" on case. Film: 16mm - silent, color, circa 1973 (Box 11, Item 8)
    - Aerial views of campus. Taken by Jack Hutchison. Film: 16mm - silent, color, 1947-12 (Box 11, Item 9)
    - Label "Campus scenes Oct '04" and "Thanx Bob." Digital Video: MiniDV. 60 min color, 2004-10 (Box 11, Item 10)
    - Inspection of first couple dozen feet shows man in lab coat in lab then microscope. Reel appears to contain at least 6 film segments separated by white leader. Metal case labeled: tape with handwritten label - Historical scenes from WSU Campus circa 1959 (Box 12, Item 1)
    - Inspection of first couple dozen feet looks like a political convention with people holding signs for Maine, Puerto Rico and campaign posters "Kennedy for President." Reel appears to contain at least 8 film segments separated by white leader. Metal case l, 1960 (Box 12, Item 2)
    - Inspection of first couple dozen feet shows Baseball game, but may be another film on reel. Metal case labeled: masking tape with handwritten label - Historical shots of WSU Campus and KWSU Filming of "Tolstoy." Film: 16mm - silent, color. ~1600 ft=45 min, 1960 (Box 12, Item 3)
    - Inspection of first couple dozen feet looks like Vet School film with 2 people in medical scrubs (vet and vet tech?) working on front paw of awake beagle. Metal case labeled: tape with handwritten label - Films of events on the WSU campus, time unknown, c, circa 1960 (Box 12, Item 4)
  - SUBSERIES 3.1: GREENSPAN STOCK FOOTAGE / B-ROLL.
    - Inspection of first couple dozen feet shows what looks like milking machine on udder. Reel appears to contain many film segments. Metal case labeled: masking tape with handwritten label - Historical shots on WSU Campus about 1970. Film: 16mm - silent, col, circa 1970 (Box 12, Item 5)
    - Kids on Campus Fall 1994. #2. Video: Betacam SP. 30' tape, 1994-09 (Box 13, Item 1)
    - Television Story - "Action for Children's Television" on post-it note. #3. Video: Betacam SP. 20' tape, 1994-09 (Box 13, Item 2)
    - Black Studies Class - Interview w/ 3 students. #4. Video: Betacam. 20' tape, 1994-09 (Box 13, Item 3)
    - Basketball Game. #5. Video: Betacam SP. 30' tape, 1994 February 26 (Box 13, Item 4)
    - Interviews. Spin of Atrium in Library. #6. Video: Betacam. 20' tape, 1994-09 (Box 13, Item 5)
    - Jesse Harris - ASWSU President at Computer. #7. Video: Betacam SP. 20' tape, 1994 October 06 (Box 13, Item 6)
    - Classroom - white male teacher. Walking down hallway. Interview. #8. Video: Betacam. 20' tape, 1994-09 (Box 13, Item 7)
    - LeRoy Ashby classroom - white male prof. #9. Video: Betacam. 20' tape, 1994-09 (Box 13, Item 8)
    - Fight song. Hospital. Vet Clinic. #12. Video: Betacam. 30' tape, 1994 April 14/1994 April 15 (Box 14, Item 1)
    - Lab shots. #14. Video: Betacam. 30' tape, 1994 April 14/1994 April 15 (Box 14, Item 2)
    - Campus shots. Interviews. #33. Video: Betacam. 20' tape, 1994-09 (Box 14, Item 3)
    - Interviews. #35. Video: Betacam. 20' tape, 1994-09 (Box 14, Item 4)
    - "Fall 94." #37. Video: Betacam. 20' tape, 1994-09 (Box 14, Item 5)
    - WSU AG/ME. #41. Video: Betacam, 1994-09 (Box 14, Item 6)
    - WSU Gilbert (?). #4. Video: Betacam SP, 1994 February 23 (Box 14, Item 7)
    - Chinese Men and Prof. Interview w. woman. #6. Video: Betacam SP. 30' tape, 1994 February 24 (Box 14, Item 8)
  - SUBSERIES 3.2: "ARCHIVAL" STOCK FOOTAGE / B-ROLL.
    - Ed Murrow Archives #1 on case. Tape label is: Ed Murrow Tape 1 Still Photos. Enclosed handwritten sheet lists 5 photos (London #1-#5) with tape counts on zoom in and out and pan. Video: 3/4" U-matic (small). 20 min., undated (Box 15, Item 1)
    - Ed-TV Ed Murrow Archives #2 on case. Tape label is: Ed Murrow Still Photos Tape 2. Enclosed handwritten sheet lists London #5-7, Korea #1-3, Portraits #1, and Misc 45-49 #2 with tape counts on zoom in and out and pan. Video: 3/4" U-matic (small), undated (5-87 on tape side) (Box 15, Item 2)
    - Ed Murrow Archives #3 on case. Tape label is: Ed Murrow Still Photos Tape 3. Enclosed handwritten sheet lists Misc 45-49 #3 and 4 with tape counts on zoom in and out and pan. Video: 3/4" U-matic (small), undated (Box 15, Item 3)
    - Ed Murrow Archives #4 on case. Tape label is: Ed Murrow Tape 4 Still Photos. Enclosed handwritten sheet lists 4 informal photos then 5 52-59 photos with tape counts on zoom in and out and pan. Video: 3/4" U-matic (small). 20 min., undated (Box 15, Item 4)
    - Ed Murrow Archives #5 on case. Tape label is: Ed Murrow Tape 5 Still Photos. Enclosed handwritten sheet lists 52-59 photos (#6-7) then 61-64 (#1-4), and Family #1 with tape counts on zoom in and out and pan. Video: 3/4" U-matic (small). 20 min., undated (Box 15, Item 5)
    - Ed Murrow Archives #6 on case. Tape label is: Ed Murrow Tape 6 Still Photos. Video: 3/4" U-matic (small). 20 min., undated (Box 15, Item 6)
    - Ed Archives #8 on case. Enclosed handwritten sheet seems to list 14 photos of Murrow (such as "Murrow in CBS office") with tape counts but no detail on camera directions. Video: 3/4" U-matic (small). 20 min., undated (Box 15, Item 7)
    - Ed Archives #9 on case. Enclosed handwritten sheet are tape counts for photos of "Ed" (Murrow). Tape Library B-4500 on side of tape. Video: 3/4" U-matic (small), undated (Box 15, Item 8)
    - Ed Archives #10 on case. Enclosed handwritten sheet are tape counts for photos of "Ed" (Murrow). Video: 3/4" U-matic (small). 20 min., undated (Box 15, Item 9)
    - SM-401 Ed Archives - Going to N.Y. stuff, WWII, young Ed, etc. SM-401 on tape. Handwritten scrap of paper inside: SM-401 fuzzy Ed and Hitler, WSU #2 Pamphlet, Ed Arch 6? New York ship shot. Video: 3/4" U-matic (small). 20 min., undated (Box 15, Item 10)
    - WSU Archives #1 is only labeling. Video: 3/4" U-matic (small). 20 min., undated (Box 15, Item 11)
    - WSU Archives #2 is only labeling. Video: 3/4" U-matic (small). 20 min., undated (Box 15, Item 12)
    - WSU Archives #3 on case and tape. Tape Library B-4470 on case spine. Video: 3/4" U-matic (small). 20 min., undated (Box 15, Item 13)
    - MASC Grain Elevators/Still Photos on spine. KWSU-TV field tape also on case with G.R.J. #37 and these are repeated on tape. Video: 3/4" U-matic (small). 20' tape?, undated (Box 15, Item 14)
    - Loading Grain/Port of Lewiston. Video: 3/4" U-matic (small). TRT 17:24, undated (Box 15, Item 15)
    - Field Work Spring/Fulfs Farms and Tractor Testing #3 also on spine "MASTER Do Not ERASE." Also marked "Contract Productions" - is this KWSU for Palouse Ag Tech?. Video: 3/4" U-matic (small). 20' tape?, undated (Box 15, Item 16)
    - MASC Spring Fields/Harvest on spine. Palouse Ag. Tech. Spring Fields 5-22-87 on tape. Video: 3/4" U-matic (small). 20' tape?, 1987 May 22 (Box 15, Item 17)
    - Wheat Fields. Video: 3/4" U-matic (small). 20' tape?, 1990 August 02 (Box 15, Item 18)
    - Wheat Fields Harvest. "Guy's tape - wheat fields etc. w/ music". Video: 3/4" U-matic. 14:00, undated (Box 15, Item 19)
- SERIES 4: LIBRARIES.
  - Holland Hole Construction. Video: S-VHS. 120' tape, undated (Box 16, Item 1)
  - F.P. Owens 90th Birthday Party. MASTER. Video: VHS. 120' tape, 1990 February 16 (Box 16, Item 2)
  - WSU Lib #1 WSU Libraries, Addition to Holland Library 1991-19?? MASTER SHOTS TAPE. Video: S-VHS. 120', 1991-1992 (Box 16, Item 3)
  - WSU Lib #2 WSU Libraries, Addition to Holland Library 1991-19?? MASTER SHOTS TAPE. Video: S-VHS. 120', 1991-1992 (Box 16, Item 4)
  - Tour of Holland Library Addition. Video: S-VHS-C, 1993 March 03 (Box 16, Item 5)
  - McWhorter. Video: VHS. 120' tape, 1992 May 8/1993 February 16 (Box 16, Item 6)
  - Omaha - FBI/Blumberg Library by Steve Huntsberry. Video: VHS. 60' tape, undated (Box 16, Item 7)
  - Steve Huntsberry - 1997 Books Stolen from Holland Library. Master without Music. Video: VHS. 5 min (Box 16, Item 8)
  - "Persona" dedication 4-7-00. "Persona" is the wind sculpture on top of Terrell Library. Video: M II. 20', 2000 April 07 (Box 16, Item 9)
- SERIES 5: PERFORMING ARTS and FINE ARTS.
  - WSU Synchronized swimming. 62nd annual show, "At the Movies." Video: VHS, 1990-04 (Box 17, Item 1)
  - Palouse Performance #115. Tom George, piano, Eugenia Bowman, vocalist, Jack Davis, clarinet. dub. Video: VHS, 1993 May 11 (Box 17, Item 2)
  - Crimson Co. #1 Sat. Note states that "At 14:00, looks like a break in control track." Video: 3/4" U-matic. 54:40, undated (Box 17, Item 3)
  - Crimson Co. Saturday Tape #2. Video: 3/4" U-matic. 60:30, undated (Box 17, Item 4)
  - WSU Concert Choir Dr. Frank Green Kimbrough 141. 1. Songfest '78 2. Puttin' on the RITZ. Video: 3/4" U-matic. 11:30, 1978 (Box 17, Item 5)
  - "Performing Arts Gala 3-28-01 Tape #1." Video: M II, 2001 March 28 (Box 17, Item 6)
  - "Performing Arts Gala 3-28-01 Tape #2." Video: M II, 2001 March 28 (Box 17, Item 7)
  - WSU Performing Arts Gala. Video: VHS. 160' tape, 2001 March 28 (Box 17, Item 8)
  - Music Frank Green RITZ #1598. Part. 1 Pivonka. Video: 3/4" U-matic. ~60 min, 19uu November 01 (Box 17, Item 9)
  - "Cougar band performance" "HALFTIME Stanford" on case. Video: 3/4" U-matic (small). 20 min., undated (Box 17, Item 10)
  - WSU Cougar Marching Band. Label refers to 5-15 sec shots of band in the stands, on field, at the Rose Bowl., 2000-12 (Box 17, Item 11)
  - WSU Fight Song. Music/No Words. Audio: 1/8" tape Standard Audio cassette. 60' tape, undated (Box 17, Item 12)
  - WSU Alma Mater. WSU Concert Choir, Dr. Frank Green conducting. Audio: 1/4" open reel audio tape, 1970 May 25 (Box 17, Item 13)
  - Art show. Film: 16mm - silent, color, 1960s/1970s (Box 17, Item 14)
  - Handwritten on case "1967 U of I Nov. 11, 1967" [Veteran's Day ceremony?] Tape leader has "WSU Band 1967 No Sound." Band in a stadium that could be U of I. Film: 16mm - silent, color, 1905 May 20 (Box 17, Item 15)
  - "Band Print No Charge 1968" handwritten on case, "WSU Band 1968 B+W No sound" on film leader. Film: 16mm - silent, b/w. 1.5" film (Box 17, Item 16)
- SERIES 6: WSU-PRODUCED NEWS STORIES AND OTHER MATERIALS.
  - Adcock Air Drilling. Note on case "Produced by WSU c. 1975 (?)" Inside case are 4x6 cards and notes about tape and drilling?. Video: 3/4" U-matic. 10 min tape (Box 18, Item 1)
  - Cougar Electronic Journal (also as Cougar E-Journal). WSU news magazine. Hosted by Al Ruddy. Video: 3/4" U-matic, 1977 May 23 (Box 18, Item 2)
  - "Cougar Electronic Journal #1." b-roll for news stories: obsidian blades, Sequim mastodon, more. Video: 3/4" U-matic, 1970s (Box 18, Item 3)
  - Keith Jackson. Funny Faces. Video: 3/4" U-matic, 1981 March 24 (Box 18, Item 4)
  - 1986 Annual Report. Master. Enclosed sheets of video clip schedule. Video: 3/4" U-matic (Box 18, Item 5)
  - Natural Resource Science. Tape notes "(for recruiting to the major) produced in 1988 or 89 by Al Ruddy narrator unknown. called "Edit Master" on case. Video: 3/4" U-matic. 8 min on case, 1991 May 10 (Box 18, Item 6)
  - Second Century Committee. Tape #1. Video: 3/4" U-matic. 60' tape, 1990 February 13 (Box 18, Item 7)
  - Second Century Committee. Tape #2. Video: 3/4" U-matic. 60' tape, 1990 February 13 (Box 18, Item 8)
  - College of Business and Economics. Advisory Board meeting #1. Video: 3/4" U-matic. 60' tape, 1990 November 16 (Box 18, Item 9)
  - College of Business and Economics. Advisory Board meeting #2. Video: 3/4" U-matic. 60' tape, 1991 November 16 (Box 18, Item 10)
  - College of Business and Economics. Advisory Board meeting #3, Talk by Manny Ferris. Video: 3/4" U-matic. 60' tape, 1992 November 16 (Box 18, Item 11)
  - WSU Communications/BDCST 465/565. Cable 8 News Edit Tape 8. Reporter Gary Burckhardt. 10 stories. Video: 3/4" U-matic, 1991 (Box 18, Item 12)
  - "A Gift of Reading." Video: 3/4" U-matic. 29:30, undated (Box 18, Item 13)
  - Dateline WSU: The Gift of Reading. Ruddy - Milligan master. Video: 3/4" U-matic, undated (Box 18, Item 14)
  - KWSU-0TV VC-32. CEJ #102. Dub News Tapes B 1." Al Ruddy, WSU News Bureau. Video: 3/4" U-matic, undated (Box 19, Item 1)
  - Earth House 1980. #5 Earth home at Waiwai [sic], campus shots, resume audition tape of Blanca Trescano?. Video: 3/4" U-matic (small). 15' tape (Box 19, Item 2)
  - Earth House 1981. #6 Earth house at Wawawai under construction. Video: 3/4" U-matic (small). 10' tape, 1980 (Box 19, Item 3)
  - Ash particles - 100 microns (larger) seen through compound research microscope. Scale shown - 100 microns btwn longest lines. Mt St Helens. Video: 3/4" U-matic (small), 1980 (Box 19, Item 4)
  - "Material for TV program about ash fall from Mt. St. Helens." Sorem/Kappe/Halvorson on case. Inside is elaborate handwritten program with tape counts. Video: 3/4" U-matic (small), 1980 (Box 19, Item 5)
  - List of tape counts with material such as "Smith - tree fruit 2:00." Likely Mt St Helens. About plants. Professors Smith, Mack, Engibous. Video: 3/4" U-matic (small), 1980 (Box 19, Item 6)
  - College of Business and Economics. Ribbon cutting to Todd Hall Addition. Video: 3/4" U-matic (small). 20' tape, 1990 December 14 (Box 19, Item 7)
  - WSU Tri-Cities Ground Breaking. Tape #1. Video: 3/4" U-matic (small). 20' tape, 1990 March 28 (Box 19, Item 8)
  - WSU Tri-Cities Ground Breaking. Tape #2. Video: 3/4" U-matic (small). 20' tape, 1990 March 28 (Box 19, Item 9)
  - SALC Professor Protocol 1992 Contract Productions. Note on tape: tape made for SALC, 1992, gives students advice on how to deal with professors. Video: 3/4" U-matic (small). 20' tape (Box 19, Item 10)
  - Professor Protocol - A SALC KWSU Production. Video: VHS. 120' tape, 1992 (Box 19, Item 11)
  - SALC Professor Protocol 1992. Proposal from SALC to Radio-TV for production help, script, notes on production. Paper. (Box 19, Item 11a)
  - "Admissions #1 Pow-wow" on case. "Pow-wow in Bohler Gym - Steve Nakata asking questions" on tape. Video: 3/4" U-matic (small). 20 min., undated (Box 19, Item 12)
  - "Admissions #2 Pow-wow (continued)" on case. "Pow-wow in Bohler Gym - Steve Nakata asking questions" on tape. Video: 3/4" U-matic (small). 20 min., undated (Box 19, Item 13)
  - KWSU-TV; VC 20150. "Wheat Commission research lab biking windy wheat fields." VC 20150. Video: 3/4" U-matic (small). 20 min., undated (Box 19, Item 14)
  - Rose Festival Coronation Ceremony. Portland, OR, Amy Black, Madison H.S. Video: VHS. 120' tape, 1989 June 02 (Box 20, Item 1)
  - Stimson. Frykman. Fry. (Fry not actually on tape). Video: VHS, circa 1990 (Box 20, Item 2)
  - Project Chrysalis c/o Extended University Services WSU. handwritten on label "from Don Hanna". Video: VHS. 18:29, 1991 April 01 (Box 20, Item 3)
  - Project Chrysalis. Extended University Services address on tape. Video: VHS. 30' tape, 1991 April 01 (Box 20, Item 4)
  - Solar/Electronics Materials Lab. WSUTC-file video (7:10) dub. Video: VHS. 120' tape w/ 7:10, 1992 October 08 (Box 20, Item 5)
  - CIR/WSU Project Interactive. US West Communications out of Seattle. Dir. Walsh V92-144. Video: VHS. 19:45, 1992 October 12 (Box 20, Item 6)
  - Singer Garth Brooks. WSU (Pullman) prior to 1st of 2 concerts Aug. 7 and 8 1993 from Tim Marsh of WSU News and Info. Video: VHS, 1993 August 07 (Box 20, Item 7)
  - Jesse Harris at home 1 of 2. Label on tape and case for Tele Edit of Minneapolis (Jesse Harris was African-American ASWSU President). 1 of 2. Video: Betacam SP. 20' tape?, 1994 October 06 (Box 20, Item 8)
  - KWSU Jesse Harris at home 2 of 2 called "Computer Work." (this is field tape from camera) NTSC checked. 2 of 2. Video: M II. 20', 1994 October 03 (Box 20, Item 9)
  - WSU Homecoming Bonfire '93. Tele Edit (Minneapolis, MN) label. Video: Betacam. 20' tape, 1994 October 07 (Box 20, Item 10)
  - Museums. Video: VHS, 1994-Fall (Box 20, Item 11)
  - WSU Faculty Senate. Video: VHS. 120' tape, 1994 November 10 (Box 20, Item 12)
  - Impact of the Information Superhiway on Higher Ed. Explored at Cause '94. Video: VHS. 45 min., 1994 November 30 (Box 20, Item 13)
  - Raymond Muse History Office Dedication Ceremony. Video: VHS. 120 min tape, 1993 July 17 (Box 20, Item 14)
  - The President's Annual Leadership Conference. Video: VHS. 160' tape, 1996 September 18 (Box 20, Item 15)
  - News Segments: EMSL Dedication and Hazel O'Leary's Visit. Copy of: #3855/46 Copy for: Nathan Bauman/PNNL. Video: VHS. 00:18:00, 1996 October 16 (Box 20, Item 16)
  - WSU Projects. Video: VHS, 1996-10 (Box 20, Item 17)
  - The Road to Pullman: A Timeless Road Trip Travelogue. Film by Leslie Strom, Wide Angle Productions (Seattle). Video: VHS. 40:00, 1996 (Box 20, Item 18)
  - WSU Link II. Edited version of satellite broadcast (with time-code burn-in). Video: VHS. 56 min., 1997 January 15 (Box 20, Item 19)
  - Discarded on 7/8/2015. MOE. (Box 20, Item 20)
  - ASCCT (American Society for Cellular and Computational Toxicology? But did not exist in 1997). ASCCT Meeting 2/20/97. WHETS?. Video: VHS. 120 min tape, 1997 February 20 (Box 20, Item 21)
  - Shock Physics. Material for press announcement. Package: 4:14. B-roll: 8:44 (slated). Audio channel 2 only. Video: VHS, 1997 June 23 (Box 20, Item 22)
  - WASU Case Study. Maverick Productions, Seattle. Video: VHS. 5:06, 1997 September 18 (Box 20, Item 23)
  - WSU Cooperative Extension Highlights '97. CAHE Info. Dept. Video: VHS. 20 min., 1997-10 (Box 20, Item 24)
  - ASCCT Meeting 11/20/97. On tape has WHETS videotape label. WHETS?. Video: VHS. 120 min tape, 1997 November 20 (Box 20, Item 25)
  - WSU Mall. Video animation from Kim Singhrs and his students. Video: VHS, 1997-11 (Box 20, Item 26)
  - Gupta / Shock Physics. Raw footage. Video: VHS, 1998 April 15 (Box 20, Item 27)
  - An Issue of Substance at Washington State University. KWSU-TV. Video: VHS. 59:19, 1998 September 02 (Box 20, Item 28)
  - Sound Farming: An Investment in Our Community. WSU. VT0081. Video: VHS. 32 min., 1998 (Box 20, Item 29)
  - True Colors. Future Teachers of Color. Video: VHS, 1998 November 10 (Box 20, Item 30)
  - City of Pullman - Economic Forum, Role of the Universities in Economic Development. Video: VHS. 1:58:00, 1999 March 23 (Box 20, Item 31)
  - SpeakEasy "How to Video." Video: VHS. 6:00, 1999 (Box 20, Item 32)
  - WSU College of Agriculture and Home Economics Video for Board of Regents. Video: VHS, 2000 March 30 (Box 20, Item 33)
  - CAHE Update #6 satellite teleconference. Video: VHS. 90 min., 2000 March 28 (Box 20, Item 34)
  - CAHE Update #7 satellite teleconference. Video: VHS. 91 min., 2000 August 21 (Box 20, Item 35)
  - WSU Logo Training. WHETS. Video: VHS. 120' tape, 2000 December 18 (Box 20, Item 36)
  - CAHE Update #9 satellite teleconference. Video: VHS. 90' tape, 2001 March 09 (Box 20, Item 37)
  - Women's Leadership Forum Panel. Video: VHS. 60 min. tape, 2001 March 29 (Box 20, Item 38)
  - WSU International Textile and Apparel Association "Designers Exposed." 18th Annual Mom's Weekend Fashion Show. Video: VHS. 45:00, 2001 April 21 (Box 20, Item 39)
  - Gorilla faculty. Channel 8 News. Video: VHS, 2001 March 13 (Box 20, Item 40)
  - WSU Cable 8 footage of Memorial Service for three Students. Video: VHS. 60' tape, 2001 June 14 (Box 20, Item 41)
  - Eco-terrorism. NW Cable News/KREM (tape includes only first half hour). Video: VHS, 2001 September 08 (Box 20, Item 42)
  - Faculty Budget Presentation. Video: VHS. 120' tape, 2001 September 26 (Box 20, Item 43)
  - Jeff and Brent Trip to New York City. Video: S-VHS. 4 min., 2001 October 06/2001 October 09 (Box 21, Item 1)
  - WSU Fire Department New York Trip. Video: VHS, 2001 October 10 (Box 21, Item 2)
  - WSU Foundation. Focus Group at Robinson Research, Inc. - Dub. Video: VHS. 2 hrs, 2001 November 29 (Box 21, Item 3)
  - WSU Scholars Reception 2001. Video: VHS. Short (5')? (Box 21, Item 4)
  - Teaching and Assessing for Critical Thinking and Deep Learning. Video: VHS, 2002 February 22 (Box 21, Item 5)